Poor Third Madam was so devoted to Master in life.
And since her death,
she comes back to find Master every night.
Master.
You're back.
Come on.
Let's go check out the Dragon-Locking Well.
Wait for me!
This day
has finally come.
Third Madam.
You loved singing opera.
The last opera you sang before you died
was Cinnabar Well.
While you were singing,
you disturbed the Dragon King.
So, did you really see the Dragon King?
Why does it smell like rotten eggs?
I smell it too.
That's the smell of miasma.
Miasma?
Is your dog nose working right?
It's only found in deep mountain swamps.
This is the Li Mansion.
Never mind the swamps.
There are barely any trees here.
Where would miasma come from?
In mountain forests during summer,
the temperature and humidity are high.
The miasma in the mountains is very thick.
Once a person inhales miasma,
they'll at least fall ill,
or at worst, die.
Are you saying
Third Madam didn't die from possession?
She died from inhaling miasma?
Exactly.
Miasma causes fever,
chills, and other symptoms.
When the virus invades the nervous system,
it also causes delirium.
Third Madam's so-called possession
was actually miasma poisoning.
Then...
Then this Dragon-Locking Well...
Iron chains locking the Dragon King...
Where's the Dragon King?
And this miasma...
Where did it come from?
Since you have so many questions,
why not go ask the Dragon King yourself?
Why me?
Why not you?
Master!
My Master can't swim!
Quick, save him!
Why didn't you say so sooner?
Pull him up quickly!
Master! Wake up!
Don't scare me!
Bookworm!
Master! Bookworm!
Wake up!
Bookworm!
Is he okay?
Master!
Wake up!
Master! Wake up! Master!
I won't fight you for chicken legs again!
Master! Wake up!
Master!
What are you doing?
You do it.
You'd better do it.
I have bad breath.
Master!
Dad!
It's so good to see you.
What's so good about it?
Let me ask you.
Where is Heavenly Craftsmanship from Wenchang Pavilion?
Thieves stole Heavenly Craftsmanship.
Where is the book now?
I have no idea.
Didn't I tell you?
Guard the book with your life.
And you still have the nerve to come back?
Go!
Hurry up and get the book back!
If you can't find Heavenly Craftsmanship,
then never come back!
Master!
Master! Master!
Are you okay?
What are you doing, She-devil?
Are you trying to take advantage of me?
I'm saving your life!
Saving my life?
You were straddling me!
How could I save you without sitting on you?
Ingrate!
Dragon-Locking Well draws from this river.
Let's hurry and check downstream.
Dragon-Locking Well's water connects here.
Master, what is this place?
This pool is deep in the mountains.
It's hot and rainy,
and the air is stagnant.
In the swamp,
a lot of rotting plants have accumulated.
The dirty water with these rotting plants
will evaporate under high temperatures,
which then
forms miasma.
This miasma-filled water
flows along the bottom of the well
and into Li Mansion's Dragon-Locking Well,
filling the well with toxic miasma.
I see.
This valve connects to the Dragon-Locking Well's chain.
But
that doesn't make sense.
Why doesn't it make sense?
Didn't we swim here from the well's bottom
and find that the area around the pool
is filled with miasma-contaminated water?
I mean,
why would someone channel miasma
directly into their own well water?
You mean
someone purposely led miasma to Li Mansion
to use it as a murder weapon?
It's very likely.
Judging by the wear on this iron chain,
this water valve
was installed later on.
Someone modified the water valve.
So that means
at noon on the day of the incident,
the miasma evaporated.
That's why Third Madam
was infected and died.
The killer modified Dragon-Locking Well's valve,
diverting the sewage containing miasma
into Li Mansion's well.
The ventilation in the well was poor,
and with the scorching sun that day,
the temperature inside rose.
The miasma
evaporated from the sewage.
Third Madam inhaled miasma by the well,
and was poisoned.
Madam!
Madam, what's wrong?
What's wrong, Madam?
Before the incident,
the strange noises from the well
were made when the killer was modifying
the water channel.
The so-called Dragon King claiming lives
was actually
just murder by miasma.
So that means
Third Madam was also murdered.
She-devil,
you're the next one to marry Master Li.
How will you die?
Before I die,
I'll take care of you first.
Alright, alright, alright.
Keep going.
The killer used hidden mechanisms
to kill Mengzhu,
used oleander tea
to poison First Wife,
used a chandelier
to crush Second Madam,
and used miasma to kill Third Madam.
But this killer
never showed up.
Killing from a distance,
and attributing the four people's deaths
to ghosts and monsters.
That's very strange.
Yeah.
Now that we've cracked the killing methods
of all four murders,
who could the killer be?
In my opinion,
this killer
not only knows everyone's habits in Li Mansion,
but
he's also skilled in architecture,
chemistry,
and painting.
He can make hidden mechanisms,
and use glassware for optical experiments.
He knows herbs well
and understands plant pharmacology.
Judging from this,
the killer is not acting alone.
No, wait!
Watch out!